Hey Dad, how long are you staying?
Who's to say?
You'll probably be in tears the second I walk out the door, won't you?
I gotta pee!
Oh! Don't fall in!
Actually, I've been wondering the same thing.
How long are you staying, dear?
What's wrong?
Yuriko, am I not welcome in my home?
I'm just curious if your job is okay with you being here for such an extended period of time.
I'm home!
Oh, and I brought me a mortar along.
Whoa, really?
Nice to see you.
Who the hell are you?
What, you can't recognize your best buddy in the whole wide world?
Um, so, uh, thanks for having me.
I'll be damned, it is you!
Uh-huh. In the flesh.
Leave him alone. It's too hot to be so close.
No kidding. You could fill an Olympic-sized swimming pool with all that sweat.
Yeah, I know. But it's a cold sweat.
I got an idea.
Sir?
You and me should take a bath together.
What'd you say?
Go on. I already filled it up for you.
There's plenty of time before dinner.
Nah, I'm good.
You don't like me?
No, I think you're great.
You do?
Sweet! Then let's hop in.
Come on, Miyamura.
Oh, don't be shy.
Um, sir.
One sec.
Please don't freak out! I can explain everything!
And no, they're not Yakuza tattoos, I swear!
Oh, right.
This is probably a dumb question, but are these disposable?
It took you the whole meal to notice?
It took me until I saw his match yours.
I'm so sorry.
Oh, it's getting late. I shouldn't overstay my welcome.
You're here now. Just stay the night.
What?
Thank you, but I shouldn't.
If we let Izumi spend the night with us, Kiosuke won't have a futon.
Seriously?
So the boyfriend gets priority over me?
Are you really gonna stay?
I wouldn't want to impose.
You should! I'm cool with you sharing my room!
No way. Miyamura's sleeping with Daddy tonight.
Aww!
Okay, boys. Good night.
I know. Sucks sharing a room with an old fart.
No.
Bet you wish you were in Kyoko's room.
I'm perfectly fine here, really.
So tell me, what is it you like about my daughter?
I like that she doesn't judge people based on their looks.
Sir? Did you hear me?
PASSED OUT.
惹かれ合えばさらば知りたくない
思い出せば今もふわっと香る
君と僕は同じ色こすり
もの少し背伸びをして歩いた道
ビードロの靴 移り変わる季節模様
きっと消えない 今日は言えない
元通りにはもうできない
あの頃に隠した本物はどこ
怒ってくれない わかってくれない
思ってもただ募ってしまうだけ
懐かしいによると この歌が残る
我々を chromosomeく
ブーラから上に隠したい
うん 上にい 同時に
Those are our middle school gym clothes
See you later, alligator
Be safe
Have a lovely day
You want me to walk you there?
Follow and you're dead
See you later
Thank you for everything
Not so fast
Don't say thanks when you leave
Say see you later
I'll see you later
I sure hope so
That can't be right
They just came out of the same house together
Holy shit, Hori from class one?
Dude, I thought she was single
Hori, you've got an elective with her, right?
She's way too good for him
She only reminds me one
Yeah?
What's a grade-A chick like that doing with Miyamura?
If she's going slumming
She might as well date me
Have you heard?
Miyamura and Hori are totes a thing
You're joking!
She's with that emo-looking guy?
What is wrong with her?
Girl needs some standards
The whole damn school is talking shit
And if you and I are hearing it all
You know they are too
Well, the assholes are yapping about it in the same room
Even kids from other classes are running their mouths
Jerks
And right when
He finally
Got there
I know it's a sucky situation
But why are you crying?
Hey, calm down
It'll be okay
So, uh, Hori
Are you and Miyamura actually going out?
Yes, what's it to you?
No way!
Wow, I bet all the guys you ejected
Are crying their eyes out right now
I didn't turn down that many
Please, you can drop the modesty act
Don't pay any attention to them
They're chumps without a clue
Try and stay positive!
You and Hori both
Don't worry
I'm not bothered by what they say
Yo, Hori!
Where's the hubby to your wifey?
I wish I knew
Oh, shit, is he skipping school?
Ouchies!
Her hubby will be here after lunch
Did you have to karate chop me?
How are you doing?
What?
Hey, Miyamura
Why'd you get a haircut?
Oh, cause
It's hot
He's as hot as the weather
For sure
Then, what's with the winter uniform?
Uh, cause I'm cold
Your piercings are the coolest things ever
When'd you get them?
Middle school
Ooh, and your family runs a bakery, right?
Oh, boy
The ice queen has entered the chat
Hey, I'm getting kinda chilly
Yeah
Same here
I don't see this lasting too long
Huh, see what?
I'm not sure what you mean
You guys, I'm freezing
Miyamura
Check this
Jeez
And the academy award for the best reaction goes to...
Shoe
Oh, it's just you, Miyamura
Nice haircut, bro
You changing the game for summer?
Trying to
Tis the season for switching things up
Huh?
Did that chick just take a picture?
Here, I'll text it to ya
Stalker
Like, whoa
So anyway
Don't try to outdo the modi
Whoa
Daddy, you gotta come see this
Thanks for having me
And who the hell are you?
He's your bestest buddy in the whole wide world with a haircut
Whoa
It's Miyamura?
Why the drastic change?
She dump ya?
Poor guy
I wouldn't bring a boy I dumped over!
Huh?
Who's that?
Your side piece?
He's a friend from middle school
Hey, what's up?
Candy?
Oh, no you don't
Oh, sorry we're late
What are you doing?
Why are we screaming?
Yamuna!
How could you?
My sweet beloved long-haired friend
He's gone and loved me forever
I'm still right here
He can grow it back whenever he wants
So take it easy
Whoa
That is one big-ass bag of candy
Yeah, I won it from a contest online
I used to have even more
But I let my classmates stare into it
Go on
Pick your boys in
You pick for me
How's that?
Pomegranate?
Or perhaps fake?
You got any strawberry?
Nah, Chico took the liberty of picking through them
And claiming every normal flavor
So only weird kinds are left
Hey
What's that one?
Well
Let's see
Cheese?
Oh, wow
You know what?
Last I checked
Shinto didn't like cheese
Still don't
I would rather go bankrupt
Than choke that junk down
I thought as much
Say ah
Miyamura's feeding me candy
I can hardly believe my eyes
This may never happen again
But why is it gotta be cheese flavored?
Ow
I can't help but wonder if these guys are really friends
Is it tasty?
You know damn well that it's not
Such a big meanie
Can you try one?
What kind is it?
Ugh
This says it's clay
Clay flavored?
More like mistake flavored
I need water
Will you get me some?
Ugh, you're such a pain
Who's the one that made me eat it?
Earth to Hori
Come in
Sorry
He stole my candy
Oh, that little thief
What flavor was it again?
I've got more
Oh, I don't need a replacement
But thanks
Alrighty
Oh, you should try this one next
What do you know?
It does taste like clay
So what's the deal?
Did your fan club disband or something?
Guess the novelty of it wore off
Which is honestly fine by me
Um, you know her?
No
I don't think I do
She was definitely giving me a death glare though
But why was she giving you a death glare?
No idea
We were watching TV
And then it came on out out of nowhere
We totally flipped out
Are you doing okay?
Yeah, I'm fine
Just, uh...
Hello, Hori Senpai
What the?
Rumor has it that you're Miyamoto's girlfriend
The rumors are true
And your point is...
Sorry to bother you
Hmm
Okay
She's giving me a complex
Hey, uh...
You wanna hit up that boutique?
So, um...
You, uh...
I wanna know when you're breaking up with her
What?
You tell me when you're gonna break up with Hori this instance!
She's cheating?
Sounds like it
I'm not!
When are you ending things with her?
I'm never ending things with her!
I'm Honoka Sawada, Class 2-5
And I'll return!
Great, but you really don't have to come back
Oh, I will!
I can't wait
Hmm
So this girl is a second year?
Yeah
And she stalks me during every single break without fail
Remind me what her name is again?
My name's Honoka Sawada
There, you see?
Okay, why do you keep following my boyfriend, huh?
What exactly are you playing at?
I'm not playing
Then what do you want?
Hey, pump the hate breaks
What I want is no longer mine to have
I like you so much, but you're taken
It's not fair!
He's just a pierced bag of skin and bones!
What the heck do you see on this guy?
I had a crush on you first and like you
But jillion times more hoodies!
Blood twist!
What the...
When did you get here?
I've been here, dude
Because I knew something funny was about to go down
You can laugh it up after you get her off me
Okay, that's enough
Hug time is over
Shut it, you punk
Huh, what you call me?
A dirty punk
Let go of her!
Give her!
If you were a boy
I would have head-butted you by now
My feelings run deeper than you can imagine
And you still haven't told me what you even see in this guy!
I can't think of anything off the top of my head
You should be able to answer straight away!
She's mine!
Took you long enough, Yoshikawa
This show's basically in its final act
The end of a comedy is still a comedy
Oh, looky here, senpai
I made these sweet treats in home ec and they're all for you
Ever hear the term personal space?
And there they go again
Ever hear the term shut your face?
I'll talk all I want!
Doesn't matter if you like me hanging around Hori-senpai
Because she already said I could
Right? Remember?
Um, yeah
I do
Huh?
Come on
Don't want to be late for class
Pushy
Listen
Let's just go
It's a formal boyfriend request
Okay
Sure
Senpai!
Miyamura
Why, you obsessed a little
You have to stop popping out of nowhere
It's annoying as hell
But he's not with you today?
She went home early to get some stuff taken care of
In that case, I guess I'll make my way home too
Why are you going the exact same route as me?
You know that's my line, right?
Are you kidding?
Now that's my line!
Am I being pranked right now or something?
Don't tell me
My key
I left it inside
Thanks for the cake
That's good
So, you always invite cute girls inside and give them sugar?
As a matter of fact, it's a pretty rare thing
Hori doesn't even come over very often
Aw
Thought you guys were still in the cupcake phase
But sounds like you're already losing your flavor
She has no need to
Cause I'm usually over at her place
I see
So, do you have any siblings?
Nope, it's just me and my parents
Huh
I totally had you pegged as like an older brother
Then why's that?
You're good at taking care of people
Problem?
Hang on!
Why are you laughing?
Oh, man
Honika
You know
I used to have a brother
You used to?
He was a year older than me
Psych! Gotcha!
I made that up just now
Wait, what?
Come on, can you not take a joke?
Oh
I guess they're home
Thanks again for the snack
I'll see you around
So, Ada
Come over for cake whenever you want
Hi
The poor Sawatas
What a tragedy
It's so sad that they had to lose their eldest like that
I doubt you saw him very much because he went to a different school
How long has it been since he died?
It happened last year
Though I don't remember when
Such a nice boy
Her older brother
So, Ada
Who is it you're waiting for?
My really good friend?
Yeah, right!
You're trying to ambush Horty
That's such a negative word!
It's not like I attack her
Hey
Going somewhere?
What a shorty
You a first year?
She was a lot louder a second ago
You scared?
Aw, we're not scary
That's right
We just want to talk to you
You could at least tell us your name
Where's the harm in that?
Hey
Wanna head home?
Uh, sure
Yeah
Sounds good
That's a great idea
I was just trying to think of something to say
You're so uptight
Is it awkward for you to be around guys?
Kind of
Maybe it hasn't occurred to her that I'm also a guy
Good grief
Horty-senpai sure is late
I knew it!
Sorry for the wait
I've taken a nice hot bath at Horty's house
Naked
Big deal
I can do that too
Cannot
Just watch me
Kyoko, dear
Can we finish this gore fest later?
Nuh-uh
The rental's up after tonight
Horrorflix give me the heebie-jeebies
I can't believe my own daughter would bully me into watching these things
I wholeheartedly feel your pain, sir
You understand the pain of a man watching a movie about a girl bent on murdering her daddy?
I think you're running into things
Tell him
That's not why you like it, right?
I swear
I can relate to this main character so friggin' much
That's brutal, Horty
I put up with all your lies in the past
But not anymore!
Whoa!
And that's my cue to go buy some smokes
You don't have to wait up
Just an observation
But you rarely make any moves on me
Uh
What?
Do you want me to?
Even though she's the one who said it
She still got all embarrassed
Did you just snicker?
No
I mean, yes, but only because you're so cute
I'll bite
What kind of moves should I be making?
I don't know
Right now?
Kyoko, you got any change?
Man, doesn't get any more embarrassing than leaving your wallet behind
Am I right, kids?
Oh
Hey, what's up, sweetie pie?
Oh, God, I hurt
What, did you two get hot and heavy when I left?
Am I a third wheel?
Yes
I suddenly have the strong urge to reenact that last scene from the movie
The immortal!
Please save me!
We're gonna marathon the entire trilogy
No bathroom breaks!
No!
We're gonna be forgot to live, buddy
So make sure to do this
It's so good
Yeah
It's seen the eight of us
quiénes
Can take a look at the wrong patterns
Oh
You look well
You milk
That was
You
It's
I promise you, I'm close to you
I don't know what I'm looking for
I don't know what to say
I don't care
If youdeal with debriefing
ordu釜 ça
dipouin
いる